(Raj:)She'll love it.
(Sheldon:)-Hello.
-Hey. You're back.
(Leonard:)-How was your trip?
-It was wonderful!
(Leonard:)-Great. What did you do?
-I made a new friend
(Sheldon:)who likes trains
as much as I do,
(Sheldon:)I kissed Amy on the lips,
and the conductor played his
banjo for me.
(Sheldon:)Good night.
(Leonard:)Wait, wait, wait.
I'm gonna need more details.
(Sheldon:)Well, my new
friend's name was Eric.
Amy lips lasted like
the brownie we had for dessert.
(Sheldon:)The banjo-playing
conductor was missing a finger,
(Sheldon:)but he made up for it
with his can-do attitude.
(Leonard:)No, hang on. Hang on.
Are all those things equal to you?
(Sheldon:)Hmm...
(Sheldon:)It never occurred to me
to pick a favourite.
(Leonard:)Well, give it a go.
(Sheldon:)I can't answer that without
collecting additional data.
Additional data. You dog!
(Sheldon:)I'm not sure how listening
to other nine-fingered banjo players
(Sheldon:)makes me dog, but all right.